It's good! It'll be better to finish it!
Can the dream be fulfill
after all?
All the dreams
can be fulfilled.
To fulfill that
by the unimaginable magic bag.
I wanna fly in the sky freely.
That's carangid mosquito hawk.
Ah...l like Doraemon best.
Plan of Shoot!
News...
Big news!
Xinyetong finally announces that
she'll get married. Do you know that?
So who is going to marry?
Don't be frightened at that
after I tell you.
It's Xiushu, the best male singer!
Oh, so strange!
She should draw apart Xiushu.
Yeah, she should!
So you doubt about what I've said,
do you?
I'll show you the proofs!
You look!
What! This copy of Weekly
was published last year.
Irksome!
What...
Now Tong is going steady with Zetan,
is she?
That's just a rumor!
Actually, she is going steady
with a young enterprise!
You all were wrong! What?!
These are all rumors!
In fact, who's Xinyetong's
lover is still a riddle till now!
Stars Weekly Magazine and newspaper
are searching about this now.
A friend of my dad's
is a staffer in TV station!
He told us lots of information!
Such as something will
make us unhappy if we hear that.
What's it? Tell us, please!
Well, then you come to my home to play!
Let's gm!
I wanna go too!
No! Nobita won't be as silent as the grave
I hope you won't make rumors!
So I hope you never tell it out!
We'll keep the secret!
Actually... Really?
Is she so?
No matter how we look at her,
Xinyetong still looks beautiful
Doraemon
Please take out the secret prop
that can help us find Xinyetong.
I wonder who she's going to marry!
It doesn't matter you
whoever Xinyetong will marry!
I haven't use such props which
will help us fulfill our purposes!
But I care about it!
That's not a good rumor!
What bad rumor?
There're bad news about Tong,
my favorite. That's impossible!
There're really some bad rumors
about her.
Can't be forgiven!
So I want to confirm it,
or I'll worry about her!
Really? Yeah!
Shoot Shadow Enterprise Machine
What's the use of this?
Anyway, let's have a test!
Okay!
It's used to shoot others' shadows!
Look carefully!
Shadows...are shot by this machine?
Yeah! We'll show them to you at once!
It's Mom!
The shadow on the screen
is same as mom herself!
She's airing the clothes!
Ha...the clothes is worn to a thread!
Oh, crap! It's my clothes!
I tore it yesterday!
What shall I do? I'm to be blamed!
I have to run away!
Nobita
I was frightened!
Let's shoot Tong's shadow now! Okay!
It's there! We finally find it!
It's Tong!
Let's take a formal shooting
It was taken clearly! Let's go!
It's shown!
That's my Tong!
You can't touch the shadow!
Her shadow is swashing!
She is sitting on the car after
she has finished the shooting.
In her schedule, she'll attend the press
conference of her new songs next.
She's singing!
It'll be good if I can hear her voice!
She said hello to everyone! She said
that she was nice to meet everyone!
She gets on the car again.
So where is she going to go?
She's going to the photostudio to
take a picture for the cover of Weekly!
You can't see...
You can't see her changing clothes!
You can't see!
You can't!
She finally finished the shooting
and is going to have the lunch!
Really, she's eating the noodle!
She has it in a hurry,
because she hasn't much time left.
She has to go to the TV station to
kinescope for the best song next.
She's so busy!
Thus she apparently has no time to date.
Sure!
If she want to date, it'll be midnight
after she finished the work.
So she has to wait until night.
No way! Let's go out to play!
Okay!
Nobita, get up! Time is up!
I haven't had enough sleep!
You're irresponsible!
It's you who suggests to observe her.
She seems have go back to her home.
Looks very tired! She's poor indeed!
She seems very surprised! Why?
It seems something happened.
Let's go and have a look! Okay!
Please go back to your home immediately!
Hey... Don't be so cold to me!
Your lover came here especially for you!
I don't remember
I've ever treated you as my lover.
That's handsome actor Lumucilang!
Take a look of next week's Weekly!
That we've ever gotten married
will be wrote on it.
It's you!
It's you who was talebearing! Right?
Excuse me! Please understand my feeling.
Or I'll spread more poisonous rumor!
Well'?
Do you understand my feeling?
Help!
Who? Who is that?
Sorry to run into your yard directly!
I made the shadow to scare him!
Oh, so it is!
Thank you!
Please come in!
Shall we get in?
It's so late.
Maybe it's not so convenient.
Because I'm tired.
I want to talk some interesting things.
So come in please!
Xinyetong told us a secret.
It's about her lover.
He's living in another country far away.
But we can't tell you that.
Sorry very much!
Energetic Shill
carp flags in Suneo's home
are very beautiful!
There're so many sides of it.
My dad made to order it
for me in particular.
The one in my home has only two sides!
So is my home!
Maybe it's enough for your home!
High-class families such like us must
have so many sides of flags.
Yeah...
To think for you,
I want to lend you each one flag.
We don't want to have it. Right, Gian?
You're really my good friend.
I dreamed of have so many sides
of carp flags!
So I'll lend it to you!
Nobita, don't you want me
to lend it to you?
I don't.
Oh, so Gian, I'll lend you two of it.
Will you? Good friends shall
share good things together!
More quantities
don't certainly mean good.
As long as we hang up the carp flag,
it'll be lordly!
Oh, so
I understand why you're so angry.
What do you understand?
You aren't listening to me at all!
You just care eating.
I'm listening to you!
It's okay if it's flowing
even there's no wind, is it?
So even if there's no wind,
it'll flow too...
Do you have some good things?
Yeah, I have.
Energetic Shill
What's that?
Look carefully!
Hold it's mouth!
So it's okay?
They're flowing! Strange!
How about this?
There's no wind around!
While the carp flag can flow!
It's a miracle!
Thank you!
Yeah, invite Shizuka to have a look!
So beautiful!
Anyway, the carp flag full of energy
will be beautiful!
Suneo, look there!
There's only Nobita's carp flag
is flowing lively!
It looks like a fish indeed!
Really Unimaginable!
That's owe to Energetic Shill!
Energetic Shill
As long as you feed it with this,
it'll flow.
Oh, I see!
As long as let it drink that...
So how comes?
I want to have that Energetic Shill
so much!
Well, I have a good idea!
There have rats!
Rats...
Success...
It touch the spot of mine!
Absolutely it's they two!
Doraemon, strength up!
Doraemon,Energetic Shill has
been taken by Suneo and others!
It's bad now!
You two, hurry to take it back!
Or it'll be bad!
Why?
That guy is still stingy!
He gave me only four grains.
But it's enough that
I have only four carp flags!
Eat some more!
It's energetic flowing soup!
Here, have it!
Good...
Well'?
What shall we do? How comes?
It'll full of energy and become violent
if it has eaten more than two grains.
Get there quickly!
It's your fault, Doraemon!
My carp flag has run away.
Oh, crap! It's too late!
You, help me to catch them quickly!
I've spent 100 thousand
on these two flags.
100 thousand?
How could you say that?
Suneo took the shill away himself!
Oh, please! Mom will blame me about it!
Okay! We'll use carangid mosquito hawk
to chase them.
They're over there!
They're flying in high speed!
Let's speed up!
We've flow into the bank of clouds!
Take the airship and go fishing!
The fish jumped at the bait!
Sorry, I made a mistake.
Idiot...
Doraemon, you're nervous!
It jumped at the bait!
Nobita, you are nervous too!
Where do they fly to?
It jumped at the bait!
It's so powerful!
So heavy!
So energetic!
Nobita, don't lose hold of the rod!
Help me, Doraemon!
It's really tired to catch them!
They finally be a little good!
Anyway, hurry to catch them and
give them back to Suneo!
Oh, no!
We finally caught them,
but because the medicine still work now,
so you shall have a talk with them
in the room.
How could it be?
Our home's treasures are damaged!
How could I explain that to mom?
Feeling instrumentpanel
Shall I tell that to mom?
Good grief! Again I spent more than
I earned this month!
What's wrong with you?
I got a bad score in today's exam.
It's not only today!
You did worse today, right?
Geez!
If she's right in bad moods,
and if I tell her about that, I can't
expect how much she'll blame me.
So now I'm observing mom's feeling.
It's problem of chance!
About such things...
Feeling instrumentpanel
Though it looks like a common magnifier,
while if you use this to
zoom out the other,
then the moods of him will be embodied
by the model of the air.
Thus is convenient!
It's cloudy!
She's not in good moods.
You'd better leave it to tomorrow.
Okay!
Hey, it's Nobi's house!
Ah, it's dad! What's wrong?
What? You won a prize
of 100 thousand in a lottery?
It's so good!
The sun looks bigger too!
Say it now if want to say!
Mom!
What's the matter?
I got a bad score in today's exam.
Let it be since it's the past!
But you must work hard next time!
It process well.
It's really a good prop!
It's Shizuka!
Oh, Shizuka is crying!
Shizuka, what're you worrying about?
How could you have known that I was sad?
Sanmao of our home has lost.
It's bad now!
Doraemon, do something!
But however marvelous I am,
I'm not able to get that.
We three go to find together, okay?
I hate cats most!
Even Sanmao is Shizuka's, I hate too!
Suneo
Nobita, what's the matter?
Shizuka lost Sanmao!
Have you seen that?
Shizuka's Sanmao?
I don't know.
The weather is phantasmagoric!
Something wrong!
What's that?
You're lying, are you?
No, I am not!
Suneo
Where is the cat from?
Sanmao
It's the cat of Shizuka's!
It's so poor! It's tied up!
Thank you, Aunty!
You're so poor!
Geez! Who did that?
It's so good, Shizuka!
Yeah, thank you!
But how could you know that, Nobita?
Really Unimaginable!
By this, we can tell if others
are in good or bad moods.
Oh, so funny! Lend me to have a use.
Hey, Nobita!
What's so interesting? Tell me too!
See from this magnifier,
you can tell others' moods.
Strange! Yours is cloudy!
I was blamed by mom just now.
Lend me to have a look!
First is Shizuka!
And next is Doraemon!
And then is Nobita!
What! Everybody is same!
I want to look more kinds of weather.
Lend me to have a use!
You must return it back to me!
It begins to be cloudy!
Who am I going to zoom out?
Get off my back!
How is it now?
He thunders as he gets angry.
It's nice to play!
No, that...
Anybody helps?
It rains like cats and dogs!
Gian, strength up!
It serves him right!
So now...
What shall we do?
It's dad!
It's really troublesome!
Seems something wrong!
Yeah!
I'm back!
Welcome back!
About the color roll,
I find a wrong number
after I've checked it carefully.
Dad is so besotted!
The bank of clouds gets heavier.
It thunders.
Nobita, where are you going to?
Didn't you get a bad score in the exam?
Go to study quickly!
It's the secret passage to run away.
Nobita
Strange!
Hey, wait, mom!
Sorry, please wait, mom!
Oh, my!
Don't you think it's okay
as long as you hide yourself?
Apologize to me at once!
She blamed me in this way every time,
but I really can't endure her.
So you don't do wrongs, it'll be alright
No...
It's too late for you to say these.
Yeah, Doraemon!
Do you have any good ideas?
What do you mean?
Isn't that often shown on the film?
There must be a passage to run away
at the dangerous moment.
It's scene of running away from home.
Create some props or some machines
which can help us escape.
Do you have something like that?
You're really boring
to think those things.
Sure enough you haven't that.
I have.
Drill Worm
It's a bristle worm which can eat off
the Different Space and dig a passage.
Where would you like to dig first?
This...
I want to dig a passage to
escape from this room to outside.
Well, let's begin to drill!
Oh, you dug a big hole here!
I'm to be blamed!
Don't worry!
Even you said that.
Strange! There're no holes here.
Because this is Different Gate!
Oh, so great!
Ah,
here is inside of the Different Space!
It's so hollow!
Well...
The entrance is over there!
I've found it!
Because this is Different Space!
So great! You've dug to the yard!
Do you like it?
Yeah, it's great!
But this entrance of the hole...
Don't worry! While you're not at home,
hang up this menology to cover it!
That's okay!
Doraemon, you're so smart!
Well, so you no need to worry
whenever you're blamed.
Wish you being blamed soon!
Yeah,
mom, I haven't told you that
I got a duck in math exam last time.
Nobita
You don't need to say that willfully.
You must hide here!
Strange!
Where did he go?
I'm here, mom!
When did you run there?
I won't forgive you this time!
Strange...
Great... very successful!
Hey, wait!
Yeah, it'll be convenience if
there're such passages here and there.
So do it!
First, dig the lung!
QR'
QM!
Does it extend to the lung?
Strange!
Suneo, here, watch it!
Lend it to me to watch...
What? Isn't that the cartoon
he got from me?
Take it!
Ouch!
Who lost it... Geez!
Is that you?
No...not me!
He hasn't been back home!
I've too many books here.
Take it away!
I won't lend it to you!
He's back!
Strange! There's nothing in his hands!
Where's that cartoon?
I lent it to Suneo at a rent of 100 Yuan
What? Lent it to Suneo?
Yeah!
Who's that?
It's a interesting cartoon!
The bun is gone! Strange!
So is the book!
Oh, delicious buns!
Yeah,
bring this cartoon to Shizuka to watch.
Dig to Shizuka's house, please!
Well, I've dug it...
Strange!
Why will the water running
from Shizuka's house!
Is it here?
It extends to the bathroom!
Shizuka,
I'm not intend to peek at you here.
There's a little misunderstanding.
Don't explain any more.
Get away from here now.
Combination of watching free of charge.
Still a little far!
I bought it!
Uncle, have the book of
Comic Boy' been sold out?
They've just been sold out!
I've deposited money on purpose.
Then when will the new books be sold?
About next month!
What, next month?
It's this... I finally bought 'Comic Boy'
Suneo, I want to read too.
Let's read together!
Because we're good friends, aren't we?
This book is very popular!
They're sold out soon.
I know...
And we won't place an order on
'Comic Boy' until next month.
But I want to read so much.
That's 'Comic Boy', right?
Let me have a look! I want to read too.
Nobita, you can't read that!
What, 'Comic Boy'! I want to read...
They won't let me read!
Only Gian and Suneo
are reading together.
Anyway, I'll try to let you watch it.
Here are the screen and
the autodyne free of charge!
It's combination of watching
free of charge.
First, you'd set the screen up.
This is the autodyne!
And set this autodyne here.
So all sets!
Then turn on the autodyne!
Took it...
Zoom out the lens and pull it closely...
Okay...
After I pull the lens closer,
I saw it...
So funny! Really funny!
Funny!
It's easy on the eyes!
How poor Suneo is!
Let's set the autodyne to other places.
Now this is only a small test.
The real application of this is...
Set so many autodyne
in the cinemas all over the world,
or on the theater or
on the baseball park.
So we can watch the show free of charge.
Others such as Eden Ball Park,
National Skill Hall, or Wudo Hall
vocal concert or sports match,
all that I can watch free of charge.
That's what I mean.
I'll set it up immediately.
Wait! You have to
pay the charge of admission.
Yeah, then let's go in the midnight.
We're looking forward to it.
Wish the midnight coming soon.
Shizuka, what's wrong with you?
Why are you downhearted?
Nobita, I'd have gone to see the film
of Outspace Shark tonight.
It's a popular science film at present.
But I can't get the ticket.
Oh, you're unhappy for that.
Wait me for a while!
This is for you!
What's that?
Come to my home tomorrow! I'm sure to
make you sitting and watching.
What
I like watching pro baseball match. But
some won't be rebroadcasted on TV.
It only takes you 10 Yuan to
watch the baseball match in Eden.
Really?
And if you go to watch stately,
it only takes you 100 Yuan one year.
I want to see this vocal concert
very much.
But you have to line up one night
advanced, or you can't buy the ticket.
If you don't mind watching at my home,
this is the ticket for you.
What
Mazi looks lovely!
I'm her faithful movie fan!
Suneo, what's in your hands?
It's picture of my favorite singer idol
Mazi! Let me have a look.
No! This is my favorite picture
with her signature on.
What do these photos mean?
Oh, I can see Mazi's vocal
concert free of charge.
Can I? Free of charge?
I want to see too.
I want to see.
But you didn't lend me
the book of 'Comic Boy'
Don't say so!
I'm her faithful movie fan!
Then you'll lend me the cartoon later?
Yeah, I will. I will lend it to you.
Not only the cartons, but also the
model toys, I'll send to you.
So we have no ways.
Wait!
You can see it anytime
as long as you have this ticket.
Thank you, Nobita!
Is it true?
It's already midnight! Get up soon!
I still want to sleep.
We must set all of them during tonight.
Where shall we start to set first?
How can we get in?
Get in through the passage.
Come on!
Is it okay to set it here?
Yeah!
Now it's the cinema!
It's Outspace Shark
that Shizuka asked for.
Well,
where shall I set it?
It shall be set on a pantoscopic place.
Who's that man over there?
What's he doing there?
Hey, wait! Don't run!
Run quickly, take it easy...
Didn't I tell you not to run?
Didn't you hear that?
We're not bad eggs.
We are good eggs in fact.
Help me! Get into it soon...
Where to go?
So dangerous! I didn't expect
that there would have guards.
But I've installed the autodyne!
That's Doraemon!
Geez! Who is that?
Here's the Eden Ball Park
Set some autodyne inside and outside
the field, and some behind the Gallery
So the lens can be switch!
This time you must
pay more attention to guards.
There will be a show of Outspace Shark
in Nobita's home.
Really?
He invited us all to come to see.
I've been waiting for you so long.
Please come in to have a seat.
Come in, please!
It'll be shown now.
Strange! It's not shown on it.
Won't it...
Doraemon, what's wrong?
No films on it.
I am thinking if it will be...
I made a mistake.
I transposed the autodyne
and the communication facility.
It's crap now...
What! So we've been shown on the screen?
Story of snow-mountain.
Shizuka, I have something to
talk to you! What's it?
Come to my home to do
your homework with me.
Oh, I won't.
You said to do homework with me every
time, but you always copy my answers.
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Now I'm getting more and more worried!
What are you worry about?
The searching result shows by the Time
Machine is I'll marry Shizuka, right?
But I always don't think so.
Actually I feel it's unimaginable!
Such a good girl,
how will he be so foolish
to like Nobita?
There're so many boys better than Nobita.
You did go too far!
Don't be excited...
And about that if you can marry Shizuka,
you want to confirm, right?
I know...
It's this!
Time TV!
14 years later, on the date of Oct. 25,
Nobita and Shizuka got married.
So let's see the earlier situation.
It's adult Nobita!
Very ordinary!
That's Shizuka.
Hurry to decide! Go or not!
I do want to go,
but I'm not good at climbing the slope.
If it's the smooth ghat,
I'll have no problem.
You're not patient at all.
Then forget it.
I'll go with another friend.
Well...Shizuka.
I can't bear with it.
Let's watch the later status.
Yep.
Stage...
Shizuka is alone.
She must get lost with her friends.
At that time where's the adult Nobita?
What is he doing?
He's lying in bed
since he got a serious cold.
Really boring.
Wait, right!
It goes like this!
In this case the riddle is uncovered.
Lend me the Time Cloth, hurry!
Okay!
Next, I'll go to save Shizuka
by the Time Machine.
Shizuka will be very touched.
Then say 'What a reliable man'!
By this chance she will marry me.
That must be like this. Really perfect!
Don't come to help!
I'll save her by myself.
You mustn't come.
No problem?
I'll marry...
Shizuka, hey...
Nobita, you're coming!
As long as with me, you needn't worry.
Let me carry the luggage.
No, thanks anyway.
It doesn't matter, don't hold back.
Let me carry it.
Too ashamed!
We can't walk at will when we suffered
the trouble in the mountain.
We must confirm the directions
by the map.
Gosh!
You've taken the wrong map.
It's really like your work-style.
It doesn't matter.
The roadsign will tell us how to go.
Let's gm!
That's okay.
There's a cave over there,
let's have a rest.
Good idea!
Have a rest, have a rest...
When we suffer the trouble in the snow
mountain, the coldness is horrible.
Let me start a fire to warm us.
You must think the match has been wetted
and crinkled.
Don't worry!
I know how to start a fire.
Shizuka,
please carry here some dried wood.
Why don't start a fire?
Do you need the Lighter?
Why didn't you tell me
that you have the Lighter?!
Seeing that you're in high spirit,
I didn't want to cool you.
So cold!
Really cold!
Put on this, I'm okay.
So cold!
That's because you shouldn't have
come to the snow mountain in this.
If you don't change your clothes,
you'll die!
But I haven't any clothes to change.
Lend you my carpet! Well, thank you.
You've looked forward to that for long,
right? I've taken many tasty foods.
Really, too great!
There're the peach cans, beef cans,
also the bean cans.
Which one would you like to have?
Haven't you brought so many cans,
but forgotten the opener?
You hit home!
There're still some dried meat balls
left. I'll share one with you.
The dried meat balls?!
The snow's stopped. Let's get going!
Shizuka, watch out!
The ground became very slithery.
Nobita, are you okay?
I got my glasses lost since I fell down.
So I can't move now!
I've sent the SOS by radio.
They're coming right now!
Pay more patience!
We failed, it's hopeless!
Next what shall we become like?
Completely hopeless!
I will to marry Nobita.
Thank you.
If I don't stay with you,
you'll get in danger.
I can't have the heart to look at that.
Such a coward, I don't like!
I can't stand!
You should try your best to
learn to be more manful.
That's true.
The Money bees are working hard!
Nobita, you really like playing
the game of turning rope.
Not very much.
My pocket money was used up,
but this game needn't money.
A game which you won't
feel tired and hungry,
is only this one.
Nobita, would you like to
help me to clean the slot?
Clean the slot?
Gosh...l forgot to do my homework.
I'm very busy. Mom, you can go to
ask Doraemon!
How could you be?!
That's very easy to be seen through.
Nobita
I'll do that...
There's no money for such things,
really hateful!
And it only can make me tired.
What's this?
100 yen!
I can earn money!
Cleaning the slot is really not bad.
I'm home!
Doraemon...
Doraemon, a big discovery.
What strange thing did you find?
Such money sleeping somewhere unnoted
like this...
should be a big sum in Japan, right?
Perhaps.
So I got a very great idea.
Let's get together
all the sleeping money.
I think if we get it back to the society
it'll be very helpful for Japan.
Maybe!
So, Doraemon...
I want to do something for Japan.
Just bring out this kind of tools.
You did know how to talk!
As what you said,
I can't refuse you at all.
What's that?
Bees...
Doraemon, I'll be bitten.
The bees...
It doesn't matter.
They are the Money Bees.
They won't bite you.
Money Bees.
Money...
It found...
The money...
They'll find the money
on the ground and take it back.
They're the bees which will take money
back to home and store it up.
These guys are really awesome.
So let them start to work now!
You bees,
there's no any money in this house,
just go outside to find money
and take back to this box.
These bees will work very hard.
Let me go outside and watch
how they'll work hard.
Money...
Very good...just like this...
It found...1000 yen...
Bees, you're really very outstanding!
It found it...money...
Go to it...
It found it...
Money...
Found it.
Found it...
Money...
Take it back...
So awesome!
They could find money in such a place.
It sure is the Money Bees.
They've gathered so much money.
It only took 30 minutes.
In this case maybe we'll gather dozens
of thousand, no, hundreds of thousand
no, perhaps after a while
we'll gather dozens of million!
Our house need to be rebuilt.
And I want to go abroad for travel.
You can't!
But Mom, this is the money
being lost on the ground.
What's wrong with that? Right, Mom?
Even it's so, but you can't either.
If you don't hand the money which
you picked up to the police station,
that's just committing a crime of
usurping on the fairy money.
What?
It can't be...
I came to hand the money
I picked up everywhere.
Such an announce the finding of
lost property will bother us very much.
Why?
I came to hand the money
I picked up so sincerely.
Why will it bother you so much?
Since the finding of lost property
must confirm the place and amount.
Then you can come to make an
announce the finding of lost property.
As what you said,
there's no any method, eh?
Very sorry, because it's a rule.
Please recall again. Then hand it here.
I took the money to make an announce
the finding of lost property.
Really...
Doraemon,
what will we do with the money?
What 'what'? How to do?
Never thought it would become like this.
Where did we pick up the money?
We'd tell the certain place and amount.
How could we know?
Right, in this case, just ask the bees
to return the money.
But don't you think it's regrettable
for the money picked up hardy.
That's better than committing a crime of
usurping on the fairy money.
It's true.
No way, so we can only give up.
I really feel very sorry for you.
Please return the money to
where you found it.
What?
The bees seem to be very puzzled.
That's bad.
The bees become very angry
since we got them puzzled.
Help!
I'm sorry...
Delivery Bag
Hey, don't get so upset!
It's all in a day's work.
Let's go...
Nobita, you're blamed by your
teacher in the school, right?
Yes, I was blamed by my teacher.
Mom, how could you know?
It stands to reason.
You've forgotten your books
and notebooks at home.
You'd prepare the books and notebooks
for the next day once you get home.
So you do it before me today.
Okay.
I forgot my bag at the school.
Nobita
Why can you be like this?!
I have to do something.
What, forgot again?
Please...give me some medicine
which can make me not forget anything.
You should try your best to
do that occasionally.
Just because I can't,
so I came to ask you.
Forget it, I won't ask you.
Right, I got a good idea to
deal with the amnesia.
Really?
What's that?
Very simple.
That's okay!
Keeping this,
you won't forget to take anything.
Yes!
If you forget to take something,
you'll remember it when you see it.
So it is! I'll remember it when I see it
Someone ask me to do something.
Thank you, Doraemon.
I'll buy the Rice Cracker for you
when I return.
Thank you very much!
So I'm going to play!
Nobita is really a good kid.
What a good time!
I was in Shizuka's home and
asked her to treat me.
That cake really tasted good.
That...gift for me is where?
Gift'?
You tied a rope on your little
finger before you left.
And promised me to buy the
Rice Cracker for me, didn't you?
Right!
It disappeared, where did it fall?
You're really a talent of forgetting.
So that bothered everyone.
Such a person like you need use...
the Delivery Bag.
So you walk with this bag.
What's it?
I just forgot things occasionally,
then you put it over on me!
Don't look down on me!
I'm a boy all to nothing!
How can I take this with me?!
Listen to me!
For an example, if you forget to
take your notebooks home,
then you'll put your hand in the bag as
you're speaking 'my notebooks'.
What's the result? You'll bring out
your notebooks from the bag.
Very good, it's very good.
In this case, no matter how far
I leave my things,
I'll bring them out from this bag.
Anyway bring out your schoolbag left
at the school!
My schoolbag!
It appears!
So even if you forget something,
it'll be nothing serious.
Awesome!
Okay! I'll show it to everyone!
He goes beyond himself at once!
Miss Nobita,
you look very cute with the bag!
Are you going to play?
So cute!
Did you put a doll in it?
But it's not like what you thought.
I'll show you the very wonderful magic.
What?
He said he would perform the magic.
ls that for sure?
Yes.
I can bring out anything
from this bag for you.
He said he would perform the magic!
Also for me!
Then just be quickly!
So let me bring out some snacks first!
My snacks!
A thief!
It hurts...l got hit.
It hurts! Geez!
What?! I failed in the end!
Okay, the next is mom's glasses.
Mom's glasses.
What do you want to do?
Look, this is mom's glasses.
Great...
What?! I failed in the end!
It stands to reason that you bring
out something from the bag.
If you're performing the magic,
just bring out something rare.
All right, now that you said this,
I'll bring out that.
Do you know what this is?
Only a book!
Seems that I've seen it somewhere.
Then I'm reading!
3rd Mar. Sunny
I was looking at myself in the mirror.
How could my face be so pretty?
Stop reading! Isn't that my diary?
You're really a bad kid!
When did you steal this book
from his home?
I didn't steal! I said it to you,
it's the magic.
Really, anyone can perform
this kind of magic, am I right?
Yes! Only if we put things in the bag
in advance.
That's right!
Nobita...you did do like this, eh?
Okay, I'll bring out something else
to show you.
What, isn't that the mat?
What's wrong with the mat?
It's wetted!
This is the welcome mat of Gian's home.
Nobita, you bastard! Wait, don't run!
Glasses...my glasses.
Where is it?
Did I put it there and forget
to take back?
Nobita, my glasses was gone!
Help me to look for it.
Okay, there'll be no problem
with this bag.
I'll bring out mom's glasses
from the bag to show you.
Mom's glasses, return you.
Thanks.
Nobita, you made a practical joke again.
Sorry.
Don't run!
With this, no matter where you go...
What a convenient bag!
So lend me to use for a while.
After all the bag is more
suitable for mom to use.